asiflex.com 2019-05-07

# Privacy Statement

Privacy Statement
Application Software, Inc., dba ASI and ASIFlex (collectively referred to herein as "ASI") created this privacy
statement because of our commitment to your privacy. This privacy statement covers the collection and use
of your private information and discloses the privacy practices for the asiflex.com domain, as well as our
mobile application and the mocafe.com website.
This statement is meant to notify you about the following:
     •    Use of personally identifiable information that is collected from you through the website;
     •    With whom the information may be shared;
     •    Your choices regarding collection, use and distribution of the information; and
     •    Security procedures in place to protect the loss or misuse of information under ASI’s control.
If you feel that we are not abiding by our posted privacy policy, please contact us by email at
asi@asiflex.com or by calling 800-659-3035.
Information Collection and Use
ASI is the owner of the information collected on this site. However, if you are a participant in your
employer’s plan, then your employer also has access to most of the information collected from you on this
site. We will not sell, share or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this
statement. ASI collects information from our users at several different points on our website and will advise
you if you are leaving our site to go to another site.
Benefit Elections
To make a benefit election, you must have logon access to our site, and must have provided contact
information (like name and mailing address) and possibly financial information (like bank account name and
account information). This information is used for benefit and claim payment purposes. If we have trouble
processing a claim, this contact information may be used to get in touch with you.
Registration
In order to use our website or our mobile application, you must first complete the registration. During
registration you will be required to provide certain information such as employee ID number, email address,
etc. This information is used to fulfill service requests. ASI cannot process your online requests and/or
claims without the registration information or allow access to the secure portion of our website, as we need
to verify status and eligibility.
Sharing
We will share aggregated information with our partners such as purchase trends and demographic data. This
is not linked to any personal information that can be used to identify any individual person.
We use outside companies to mail certain items such as statements to your home or office. These
companies do not retain, share, store, or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.
We contract with third party vendors to assist us in delivering our services to our customers. These vendors
include third parties, such as debit card data processors and strategic partners. They perform services on
our behalf to our employee participants and employer clients. These parties are not allowed to use
personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.
We do not ask you for, access, or track any location based information from your mobile device at any time
while downloading or using our Mobile Apps, sites, or services.
Links
This website contains links to other sites. Please be advised that ASI is not responsible for the privacy
practices of or the content included on such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our

site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable
information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing information about you. After you enter your
username and password and click the Log On button, we will use a session ID cookie to indicate the
beginning of your session with ASI and make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie
expires when you close your browser. If you reject cookies, you will not be able to log on to our site. This
privacy statement covers the use of cookies by www.ASI.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by
any advertisers or other third party sites that you may access through a direct link from ours.
Log Files
We record your IP addresses when you access our site to comply with laws and regulations. We also use IP
addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track your movement and gather broad demographic
information for aggregate use.
Surveys
We may occasionally request information from users via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely
voluntary, and you have the choice to fill out the survey anonymously. Information requested may concern
ASI’ processes, website usage, planned purchases and requested features. Contact information may be used
to verify the validity of the input. Survey information will be used for the purposes of monitoring or
improving the use and satisfaction of this ASI website and services or for future product development.
Security
Our websites and mobile application take every precaution to protect your information. When you submit
sensitive information via our websites or mobile application, your information is protected both online and
offline.
When our registration/profile asks you to enter sensitive information such as date of birth, home address
and social security number, that information is encrypted using SSL. During this process, you will be asked
to create a username and password that establishes your account. Once the account is established, you
must log on to update your profile or review account status - all of which are done on secure pages. While
on a secure page, such as the registration or “Account Detail” page, the icon on the Web browsers such as
Google Chrome and Microsoft Internet Explorer will show a 'locked' status.
While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to
protect user-information offline. All of your information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above,
is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific function - such as
customer support - are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use
password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their
password to regain access to any applications.
All employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Finally, the servers that we use to
store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure locked environment.
If you have any questions about the security of our website, you can send an email to asi@asiflex.com.
Data Retention
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If
you wish to cancel your online account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you
services, please contact us at asi@asiflex.com. We will retain and use your information as necessary to
comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy or decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner
different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will update this policy and post those changes so

that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we may
disclose it.
Legal Disclaimer
Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when
required by law and when we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current
judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our organization.
Contact Information
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:
Phone:                  800-659-3035
Email:                  asi@asiflex.com
Postal Address:         ASI
                        201 W. Broadway, Suite 4-C
                        Columbia, MO 65203
Website URL:            www.asiflex.com
Fax:                     877-879-9038
